http://www.loomissayles.com/website/about-us/privacy-policy?disp=101

About Us
Home Our MissionOur CultureDiversityCareersCorporate GovernanceEnvironmental, Social and Governance (ESG) Climate Change Guiding PrinciplesUK Stewardship Code StatementProxy VotingNews & PRSocial MediaCommunity PartnershipsNonprofit Partners Undergraduate Women’s Investment Network
Advisor Solutions
Overview
Mutual Funds
Products
Managed Accounts
ETF
Performance
Monthly
Loomis, Sayles & Company Cookie Policy
We use cookies to give you the best possible experience on our website. By continuing to browse this site, you give consent for cookies to be used.
Accept
About Us
PRIVACY NOTICE
This Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information Loomis, Sayles & Company, L.P., Loomis Sayles Distributors, L.P. and Loomis Sayles Trust Company LLC (collectively referred to as "Loomis Sayles") collects, how we may process that information and who we can share it with. This Privacy Notice also describes the measures we take to protect the security of your personal information. Personal informationPersonal information, also referred to as "personal data," means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.Types of information we collectLoomis Sayles will only collect personal information that is relevant and not excessive for the purposes for which it is collected.Please see our Candidate Privacy Notice for additional, detailed information on the personal data we collect during the recruitment process. What we use your personal information for and whyThe following table describes what we use your information for and our reasons. How do we obtain your personal information?We may collect personal information about you or your company from any of these sources:Directly by you when:You or your company engage our services or buy our productsCommunicate to us as your company's contact personWhen you use our website (please see our Cookie Policy for additional information on how we use cookies)When you speak to us on the phone or during meetingsYou apply for employment or become an employeeFrom outside sources such as:Government and law enforcement entities for purposes such as identification verification and the prevention of crimeYour employer with whom we conduct businessOur affiliated companies or agents who help us source business or service our employees and clientsSecurity and confidentialityEquipment and Information SecurityIn order to safeguard against unauthorized access to personal information by third parties outside Loomis Sayles, all electronic personal information held by Loomis Sayles is maintained on systems protected by secure network architectures that contain firewalls and intrusion detection devices. The servers holding personal information are "backed up" (e.g. recorded on separate media) on a regular basis in an effort to avoid any inadvertent erasure or destruction of information. The servers are stored in facilities with appropriate security and fire detection and response systems.Access securityLoomis Sayles limits access to the internal systems that hold personal information to a select group of authorized users who require such personal information for the sole purpose of performing their job duties.Sharing of Personal InformationLoomis Sayles may share the information you provide among our subsidiaries and affiliates as required and as permitted by law. Loomis Sayles may also share personal information with third party service providers to perform services on our behalf for the benefit of our clients and/or employees. Loomis Sayles does not share your personal information with affiliates or other financial companies for marketing purposes.In addition, Loomis Sayles may disclose personal information (i) if Loomis Sayles is required to do so by law or legal process or to enforce any rights Loomis Sayles may have against you as necessary, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, (iii) when Loomis Sayles believes disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity, or (iv) if this is necessary to protect the vital interests of a person. Third party service providers may disclose personal information to other third parties for business purposes such as: governmental authorities for immigration or visa issues, as a matter of law or legal process (e.g. to tax and social security authorities), to protect Loomis Sayles legal rights (e.g. to defend a litigation suit) or as part of litigation involving such third party; or in an emergency where the health or security of an individual or individuals information is endangered (e.g. a fire or natural disaster); or, for such other purpose required for business operation or by local laws.Loomis Sayles requires its third-party servicers to agree to comply with appropriate privacy and security standards or to undertake to provide similar and appropriate levels of protection as Loomis Sayles when processing personal information.Information storageLoomis Sayles stores personal information on servers located in the United States.Updates to our Privacy NoticeThis Privacy Notice may be updated periodically to reflect changes in our information practices or as may be required by law.QuestionsPlease contact Loomis Sayles at 800-343-2029 or via email at privacyinquiries@loomissayles.com with any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Notice.Please
click here for our Privacy Statement for California Residents.
Loomis, Sayles & Company, L.P. | One Financial Center, Boston, MA 02111
